insurancedefenselawfirm.com 2012-10-03

# Insurance Defence Law Firm | Lawyers, Attorneys, Law Firms, Legal Information | Privacy

The Insurance Defence Law Firm values the privacy of its clients and site viewers. Any of the following personal information that may be made available to the lawyer or firm when browsing or navigating the site shall be kept confidential:

First and last name

Company, home, postal or other physical address 

Other contact information, for example, telephone number, fax number, email address, and other similar information

Title or position in a company or an organization

Occupation

Industry

Personal interests

Any other information needed to provide a service you requested

Domain Information Collection

The Insurancedefence Law firm may collect domain information to enable us to analyze how our visitors use this site. This data enables us to become more familiar with which people visit our site, how often they visit, and what parts of the site they visit most often. The lawyer or firm uses this information to improve its Web-based offerings. This information is collected automatically and requires no action on your part.

Use of Cookies and Tracking User Traffic

Some pages on this site may use “cookies”—small files that the site places on your hard drive for identification purposes. A cookie file can contain information such as a user ID to track the pages visited, but the only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply yourself. These files are used for site registration and customization the next time you visit us.

Some parts of the site may also use cookies to track user traffic patterns. The lawyer or firm does this in order to determine the usefulness of our Web site information to our users and to see how effective our navigational structure is in helping users reach that information. Please note that cookies cannot read data off of your hard drive. Your Web browser may allow you to be notified when you are receiving a cookie, giving you the choice to accept it or not. If you prefer not to receive cookies while browsing our Web site, you can set your browser to warn you before accepting cookies and refuse the cookie when your browser alerts you to its presence. You can also refuse all cookies by turning them off in your browser, By not accepting cookies, some pages may not fully function and you may not be able to access certain information on this site.

Information Sharing and Disclosure

Your personal information is never shared outside the lawyer or firm without your permission, except under conditions listed below:

Consenting to share your information to a third party service provider working on our behalf to serve you.

Requiring us to provide you with a product or service.

The lawyer or firm will also disclose your personal information, if required to do so by law, or in urgent circumstances, to protect personal safety, the public or our sites.

Internet Security

The lawyer or firm strives to protect your personal information; however, we urge you to take every precaution to protect your personal data when you are on the Internet. Change your passwords often, use a combination of letters

Protecting the Privacy of Children

Children under 13 years old are not the target audience for our Web site. To protect their privacy, the lawyer or firm prohibits the solicitation of personal information from these children.

Links to Third Party Sites

This site may contain links to other sites. The lawyer or firm does not share your personal information with those Web sites and is not responsible for their privacy practices. We encourage you to learn about the privacy policies of those companies.

Changes to this Privacy Policy

The Insurance defence Law Firm reserves the right to change, modify or update this policy at any time without notice. Any substantial changes in the way we use your personal information will be posted on this site. If you have questions or concerns about our Privacy Policy, please email us at the contact information on the site.
